[Music]
hello everyone this is Rahul Zara from
Sheran welcome back to exciting 3
actionable stock
updates 3 basically means right sector
right quality and right valuation these
are our investment
ideas today we have an update on IC
Lombard our analyst maintains buy rating
on icsa Lombard with a price target of
rupees
1540 higher investment income and lower
underwriting losses led to strong
earning speed in quarter 2 of FY 24
however fet was down by 2% year on year
mainly due to low tax rate in the base
period profit before tax grew by 26%
year on year the company's leading
premium market share in the industry
with secular growth potential its profit
focus with a profit share that is almost
five times its premium market share and
its leading Roe profile makes it a
compelling investment we expect healthy
premium growth led by investment in
distribution Channel and benefits acre
from past investment in technology
gradual Improvement in Combined ratio
should boost profitability further we
expect the company to deliver
medium-term Roe of 18% the stock has
outperformed the broader indexes in last
one year and it currently trades at 32.7
times fi 24 EPs and 28.8 times it's FY
25 estimated
EPS next on radar is ultratech cement
our analy maintains a Buy on ultr Tech
with an unchanged price target of rupes
9,500 considering its long-term growth
potential and positive demand and
pricing environment in the medium term
the company reported an inline
Standalone revenues for quarter 2 led by
strong volume growth operational
profitability marginally lag due to
higher than estimated PNF cost and other
expense we expect strong demand
environment for second half of f24 while
higher spot cement prices comp compared
to quarter 2 of f524 average provide
operational profitability growth Trail
bits it Revis phase two expansion of
24.4 mtpa remain on track and is
expected to go on stream in a phed
manner by fi25 and fi 26 further the
next phase of expansion is likely to be
announced before this calendar year
end for more detail disclosures and
disclaimers please refer to our research
report or contact our nearest
branch please read the risk Disclosure
document issued by sebi and relevant
exchanges and terms and condition on
share.com before
investing thank you for watching to keep
up with the latest from sherhan make
sure you subscribe to our Channel you
can also download the shareon app for
all your trading and investing
[Music]
needs investment in Securities Market
are subject to Market risks read all the
related documents carefully before
investing